{
    "id": "d25b42472c3342a5bbac389303e2c4f2",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is very …………………… and he is very short.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know how …………………… he is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "young"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is twenty-three years ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "young"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We use scales to measure how …………………… things are.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "light",
                "heavy"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the …………………. of a football field?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "length",
                "height"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is six feet …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………….. is he?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got beautiful ………………….. legs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That tree is about 60 feet ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The garden has got very ………………… walls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "tall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}